Thank you for watching!
Nogizaka Oseibo Grand Prix
The Oseibo Grand Prix is a project in which the second term students show their gratitude to their favorite senpai for all the help they have given to them.
As the legend of Valentine's Day goes, there was a big tangle of love up to this point
A series of shuraba (drama) scenes
How will tonight's drama end?
Only 4 students remain
Who are Okamoto's seniors who have helped him?
Please raise your hand
Aiyakatta
I'd like to meet him.
Sakaguchi, you're up
Sakaguchi and Kuromi are running for office for the first time
Come on, Sakaguchi!
I've been waiting for you.
What's the delay?
What's going on?
Hina-chan, you've been telling me since the very beginning that I was your favorite.
That's so sad.
Something decisive.
It's pretty strong, but still...
There's a two-shot of me on the back of Hina-chan's phone case.
There it is.
I saw it.
I did.
It's still there.
My phone case is a little dirty right now.
It's not in there right now.
Where's the Cheki now?
It's at home.
Oh, Cheki's at home.
Oops!
No, it's not... it's on the screen above where you sleep.
Take it, take it, take it, take it...
Take it, take it, take it, take it.
Take it, take it, take it, take it, take it.
Like this
On the picture table.
No, no, no.
Come on, Kuromi.
No... on my birthday... you sent me a message right at midnight.
Tell him I'm here to get the first one.
What?
I asked him, and he looked at his watch and said he sent it right at midnight.
He also said he's always happy to be with you.
Seriously?
He said she's so cute... and touched her face a lot.
He spoiled me.
He spoils me.
He touches my face.
His face and hair are so beautiful.
Seriously.
Wait a minute, while Kuromi's talking.
Hamot's hands are sweating like crazy.
No, he's not.
What?
Sweaty hands all at once?
I don't sweat that much.
But I couldn't stop sweating from the grill.
Since a while ago, when Kuromi started talking...
No, no...
Oh, no.
And we couldn't have dinner because our schedules didn't work out, but he was the first one to offer to take me out.
Is that right?
Yes, that's right.
Really?
Oh, really?
What kind of yakiniku do you go out to eat?
I see... but here's a yakiniku I haven't been to.
I wonder what the data says about that.
If I had gone, it would be yakiniku.
If he went there, it's confirmed
Which one is Okamoto's true love?
Which is it?
Ah!
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Odachi on the black body
Okamoto gives a macaroon to Sakaguchi, who has been his favorite since he joined the group
Sakaguchi, who has been his favorite since he joined the group, with macaroons to thank him.
Okamoto also said no, his hands were sweating like that when he was with the black body
He really can't lie.
And the last one, too.
No, you can't!
Next is Ogawa, the youngest, the senior who took care of him...
The youngest!
There's a lot of them.
The ones who came forward with confidence...
Including Umezawa, who's running for office for the first time.
Let's start with Umezawa.
Why Ume?
I love her so much, I honestly don't care what Anja thinks of me.
I don't really care what Anja thinks of me, and I came here to tell you how I feel.
Most recently, it's been Satsuki.
Anja wanted to have dinner with Umezawa.
You should go.
You haven't?
No.
If you did, where would you have gone?
Afternoon tea.
I don't want her to be a part of something.
I'd like to take Anja somewhere like that.
But I'm sure she doesn't hate me.
So I thought it'd be nice if she got it.
And Sakaguchi...
What? You just got it.
I know I have a lot of rivals.
But I'm so, so, so happy for Anya.
I'm so proud of her.
At the Under Live, I get a badge with a picture of a different girl's face on it, and everyone can choose who it's on.
But Anya came to the store saying "I'm wearing Tamami's badge".
We also went out together.
Where did you go?
At the donut shop.
Huh? Donuts?
I didn't see any doughnuts until now.
No doughnuts.
Is it going out? Isn't it big?
It's huge.
Come on, Kaede Sato.
It's your first time, right?
It's my first time.
Here we are... here we are.
Here? Why?
But there are many Anja's mothers.
Wait a minute... there's only one mother.
I'm well aware that there are many mothers who care for her.
They're all here in Nogizaka.
But recently we found a common hobby.
We found a common hobby.
She likes Harry Potter.
We share a common hobby.
I promised to go to a Harry Potter play with him.
I see.
The Harry Potter show is a lot of fun, so please go.
Please do.
Are you going?
I haven't.
I definitely have plans to go.
I see.
So this is where the regulars come in.
Here they come.
Black Sea.
Aya was the first one I had dinner with.
Aya? You went?
He took Tomisato with him.
The way she said it, she sounded like a woman president.
That's right.
He gave her a plate for the first anniversary of her first term.
At that time?
You got out a lot, didn't you?
Yes, we did.
It wasn't yakiniku, but we ate meat.
You went out to eat meat?
I don't know.
I'm out.
It's been a while.
Yes, it has.
But you came here to end it.
Yeah, to finish it.
Rust.
This is the real deal.
First of all, the introduction of the first student...
Here we go.
There's this pattern, too.
There were a few people who were introduced.
We also went together to pray for a hit.
Some of them were praying for a hit.
I also gave and received birthday presents.
And I remember one of them mentioned my name to a senior whom he admired.
When was that?
That's important.
I've been saying that for a while.
I'm in.
I'm pretty sure it's Yasuko.
I'm sorry about this.
It's confession time.
Okay.
Hello.
Who's the popular Ogawa?
Who the hell did they pick?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
uro
mar
dasel
I know you feel that the creek has been taken away from you, but I'm still going to go to the creek in the future.
No, there was someone who came here to make a decision
Ouch...
I'm so nervous
I'm getting a little nervous
I'm getting a little dizzy.
And Ogawa confessed her feelings with a year-end gift.
Why did you choose Sakaguchi?
Because I like him.
Straightforward!
Seems kind of difficult.
We went out recently.
We went to a couple of cafes.
We talked a lot.
Sakaguchi is surprisingly caring.
He told me to go out to eat with my seniors.
He's such a big fan of me.
I couldn't go talk to them myself, but...
But thankfully, everyone says how cute I am.
But I usually end up just saying how cute they are.
I can't go on from there.
What an extravagant problem!
It's true.
Tomisato was the next to receive a year-end gift.
The senior who wanted Rick the most came in sixth place.
Six, huh?
They're all the same height.
They're from all genres.
Why is that?
As you can see, he's very charming and a people pleaser.
In a good way.
But when we were on tour...
I knew she was saying how cute and adorable Arya is.
She seems to be good friends with Kaede and calls me "Ume".
She said she had something to say.
So don't just be cute to Arya, please be cute to me too.
What's that?
That's amazing.
It's like an indirect confession.
Yes.
It's a hit.
Wait a minute...but she came out in that episode.
Are you good friends with Kaede Sato?
I'm here with my heart set on fire.
There it is, my true love.
So it's your true love.
My true love.
Why?
I don't often go for younger guys.
But you were the first junior to come on to me.
I want to return the favor, and we've been friends for a while.
We went to an amusement park together for a photo shoot.
I gave him a bear T-shirt as a gift in return.
He's been wearing it a lot.
I talked to her manager, and he said she wore it two days in a row.
Wow, that's a lot of clothes!
He usually doesn't have any.
I still have a lot more!
We went out to dinner.
There it is...
Shabu-shabu.
I don't think so.
If it's yakiniku, I'm sure...
Afterwards, it was summer, and he suddenly asked me if I wanted to do fireworks.
I don't care if it's Tokyo or something.
I'm sure he'd be happy to.
I'm sure it's far away.
You're so calm.
It's like we're friends.
It's fine.
But is this area strong?
Yes, it is.
I went to a pizza place with him.
We have pizza, and he came to my house.
You came to my house?
Is this big?
It's huge.
We'll cook dinner at my place.
I play guitar.
You play guitar?
That's enough.
You've done that before.
I played guitar and you sang.
Oh, you're doing the class.
They're pretty lovey-dovey.
Then isn't the second half weak?
Weak, very weak.
I haven't heard anything yet. Are you okay, Shibata?
I'm fine.
From Chiba.
No, no, no.
Weak.
It's impossible if you're from Chiba, too.
And he's the first one to speak.
The very first.
Yes, and he went for the sesame exercise.
It was the first move.
I hope a lot of people will come.
Yes, sir.
Now, Mr. Kurokai, is there anything you want to tell us about the episode?
I was asked to use the hairdryer at the hotel.
I got a sunburn.
Please use the hair dryer?
I don't get it.
You're acting like a servant.
That's what I said.
I don't get it.
It's called "half-dried" hair.
I went to Mr. Kurokai's room.
He said he'd dry it for me.
And you dried her hair?
I did, and I even dried it while watching TV for a second.
That's amazing.
He came to my room and we ate takoyaki together.
He's going to his room.
That's pretty good.
I don't know. I don't know.
They call me and talk to me about things I'm worried about.
He asked me to come to his room during the tour, so I called him.
Please come.
You know, the Black Sea... you're used to it.
No, no, no... it's the other way around.
If it's you, Seimin, will you be okay?
Maybe not.
It's not true, is it? Yes, it is.
What do you mean?
I've been standing next to you at the Under Live.
After the show, he asked me if I thought I was the best friend he'd ever had.
Did you say we were the best of friends?
Wait a minute.
You said we've always been pretty good friends.
So maybe that's how you really feel.
You talked for three hours in the hotel?
I think he's number three.
But did he tell you about Seimin?
He told me.
He told you?
Did you use the word "number one"?
I did.
Wow.
It's still a big one, though.
It's a deal.
I said we're gonna decide on this one, too.
Oh, no, I've already decided on this one.
What's the plum? Why did you say that?
I don't remember either.
Is Tomisato's true love among them?
Who is Tomisato's true love?
He's on the move.
He's gone to the back.
No? Is it black?
No?
I'm out!
Promi didn't work?
I knew you were competing with Kaede for the first place.
Okay, guys...
What did they say about the semis being number one?
Well, I don't care if I'm not number one.
Wait a minute, Cicada.
Let's be friends forever and ever.
Tomisato chose Sato Kaede.
What's the reason?
I knew that Kaede would help me during the underdrama period and so on.
What I couldn't do during the rehearsal...
After the rehearsal, she would help me to do the things I couldn't do.
She helped me a lot.
I'm so glad.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Kuromi.
Don't worry, I won't keep such a distance.
On the contrary, I'm afraid.
There's only one gift left, and the last one is Okuda.
Grandpa...
Okuda?
Okuda's crying, too.
Okuda, too.
Now we'll get a five-star mother.
Two candidates have already won and two have yet to win.
Now, 4...
Yoda is a 5-star mother killer.
I'm sorry...
Are you going to get it?
We haven't talked much.
But we had a chance to talk for the first time at rehearsal.
We talked a lot and massaged each other's calves.
That's great for a junior.
I was happy, too, and afterwards he gave me a pair of dumpling socks.
Why? Because...
I thought of Yoda when I think of gyoza.
Oh, so you're not from Utsunomiya or anything?
No, no, no. That's not what I'm talking about.
I was just shopping by myself.
Oh, you found it.
Yes. We talked the other day.
I thought I could use this as an excuse to go talk to her again, so I gave it to her.
He's strong. He's strong.
It's amazing what you can do here.
Hey.
Here we go again.
It's the first time.
And you're the first student to go talk to her.
I see.
And I like her singing voice, and the way she dances and expresses herself during live performances.
I often tell her that.
That makes me happy too.
From here, right?
Let's see, Kron.
We had dinner together just the other day.
What's that?
He said it was the first time he'd had dinner with a senior.
He's here.
He went out with me.
What?
Sushi.
That's great.
It's my first time.
It's not data, but...
Also, Iroha-chan encouraged me a lot during rehearsals at the Under Live and so on.
Encouraging?
What?
About me.
When I cried, Iroha-chan came up to me and encouraged me.
And in return, when Iroha-chan started to cry during the MC at the Under Live, I was hitting her right from the side.
I told her why everyone was looking at me.
That sucks.
How confident are you?
About 75%.
That's pretty good.
That's pretty high.
Come on, Kiyomi.
About 80%.
How many episodes are we talking about?
That's what I'm talking about.
I've been standing next to you at Under Live for a long time now.
What's your position?
I really respect and love the Iroha girls, and I don't know if I can always convey that, but...
Did you say that? Have you ever said that in words?
Not really.
But yesterday, when we were watching the play together...
You said that yesterday?
And today we've been seeing each other a lot.
I wonder which one it is.
Okuda said I shouldn't do it.
They looked at each other 15 times today.
That's for sure.
I'm out.
Who'll get the last gift?
It's moving, it's moving, it's moving.
Who's there?
Is that...
Is that Yoda?
Wait a minute.
I got a semi.
This way.
Got it!
Thank you for your hard work.
They'll be here.
I'm sorry.
It was nothing.
Okuda, I thought our eyes met. Were you looking at me?
But our eyes met.
Why did you look?
I'm glad you're smiling so much.
Thank you so much.
And Okuda thanks Kuromi for her love.
I'm happy for you, Kuromi.
I'm glad.
The Kuromi's.
You must get nothing from me.
Tell me again what you gave to Kromi
As Kromi told me earlier, it was the first time I went out to eat dinner with him, and he was my senior.
First time we had dinner.
That's strong.
During the live performance period, you were really kind not only to me but also to everyone.
I really respect that.
I want to be a kind person like you.
I'm so happy.
Okuda, I've been crying since I arrived here.
What was that at the beginning of the wave?
I had seven presents.
I didn't think I'd be able to eat anything.
You're so kind.
That's nice.
I'm sorry, but we all love to do that kind of thing.
But, you know, the world's not an even playing field.
It's cold.
That's cold.
Sorry.
So again, everyone did their best to give us variety.
The bond between seniors and juniors will be indestructible from now on!
That's right! And now, it's time for our host, Bananaman, to welcome you to Nogizaka Chiken Chugaku.
It's nice to meet you too, Nogizaka-chan!
Nogizaka-chan.
Oh, they're here.
The new uniforms!
I'm going to monopolize it! I'm going to monopolize it!
I'm going to monopolize you!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm talking to you.
I've been doing this for years.
No, no, I just thought the uniforms were new.
I knew you'd ignore me in that situation.
I thought he didn't respond.
Then, Mr. Himura, please tell us what you're going to do today.
Hit project for the 34th single.
The hit project.
Thirty-four.
We do this for every single.
This is a regular project.
This time, the 34th single to be released on December 6
Moro
Polyp
No, it's not.
No, no, no.
You know, if you have a ledger camera, they can take pictures.
For polyps.
Some people have so many, they can't take more than a few.
I had about six.
Yes.
Polyps.
They take a picture of me with everyone else.
I have polyps.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Pray for the 34th single fit!
Double-centers join forces for Japan's biggest staircase challenge!
Stairs!
Oh no, we're not climbing stairs!
Thank you very much!
This time, we aim for the highest slope in Japan
The challenge is to climb the 3333 steps of Japan's tallest staircase in Kumamoto Prefecture!
We worked together as a double-center team to complete the 10 challenges
while clearing them.
We have a fixed time to return home
We aim to reach the top by then.
By the way, if you fail a challenge
You have to go back 100 steps.
What?
If you get stuck on the 100 steps...
If you come back, you have to try one more time.
You can't go on to the next step until you succeed in the challenge.
When you do a challenge, you don't just climb.
I can't imagine doing anything at all.
I usually take a short walk, maybe 3,000 steps.
So?
Maybe because I walk too slowly.
So, I'm going to take the stairs to the top of Japan and the 5th time.
Here it is...
When you look at it up close...
It's amazing!
The angle...
Can you do it?
The 3,000 stairs we're going to challenge this time...
After the start, you can't see the whole picture.
The top of the mountain path is a go.
How did you make this?
Let's start climbing the biggest staircase in Japan!
Can you do it?
Let's get off your butt.
This looks like a hit project.
A shrine?
We're climbing!
He's climbing up.
It's about a hundred steps too high.
How's it feel? How does it feel?
It's like a field trip.
Not even close.
I wonder if it's really up there.
What's this all about?
First of all, I climbed up to around 100 steps smoothly.
That's a lot of work, isn't it?
It's a lot of work.
I'm so tired.
I know.
Yes, I do.
But look, look, look.
100 steps.
Oh, my God.
How do you read that? Beans?
Oh, there's something in here.
"Gururukuruma Curtain," Mr. Car.
For each guest group?
That's what it means.
That's nice.
You see it a lot.
I see.
Each group has a single CD, so if you go up 3300 steps, you can switch back and forth through the history of Nogizaka up to the 33rd CD, and when you reach the goal, you'll be one step closer to the 34th CD.
Oh, you've got it all figured out, haven't you?
That's great!
You've been waiting for this... the 34th one.
Why is it just right?
You've been waiting until the 34th one.
2010.
Let's take a good look at it and get on with it.
You haven't been overlooked yet, have you?
To the guests.
I'm so happy for you.
And they arrived at the 192nd step.
You look totally awesome!
I did it.
I did it!
There's a black box that doesn't look very natural!
So this is the first challenge!
What is it?
Let's take turns saying the title songs of all 34 singles in order from the first one at the double center, without making any mistakes!
Oh, no!
Oh no!
Finally, take turns saying the titles of the songs in order from the first to the last, and if you can say them without making any mistakes, you've cleared the challenge!
I'm a little sorry to the past seniors.
It's the name of the title song, isn't it?
I can't say 34.
You have to say it.
You have to say it, but in order.
I know.
There's a video of it.
I remember if it was after Basra.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You have to make a lot of excuses, and if you make a mistake, you have to go back 100 steps and start the first challenge.
Guruguru Curtain
Run, Baisic!
What? I haven't made a mistake yet.
That's right, just run.
I thought it was careless.
But it's just a run and you're here... and you're the second one.
I wasn't born a pea.
That's funny!
Because of Pea's unbelievable careless mistake
The two of them were already in the age phase of 100 steps back.
7×8×9×10×11×12×13×14×15×16×17×18×19×20×18×19
I'm back a lot.
We're back to where we were before the first one debuted.
We are qualified to climb this hill!
Next time: Infinite staircase loop to hell
Will the two of them make it to the finish line?
Don't cry either!
Music video of the latest Gokisei song is now available!
Don't miss the repeat distribution of newcomers!
Gokisei no Okudaira Ip
I recently had a day off.
I was looking up where to go out
and the day is over!
Please let me know where you guys recommend!
Please subscribe to my channel!